Privacy Policy
==============

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Last updated November 15, 2023**

This privacy notice for Fishhook, Inc ("**we**," "**us**," or "**our**"), describes how and why we might collect, store, use, and/or share ("**process**") your information when you use our services ("**Services**"), such as when you:

* Visit our website at [https://www.fishhook.us/](https://www.fishhook.us/), or any website of ours that links to this privacy notice
* Engage with us in other related ways, including any sales, marketing, or events

**Questions or concerns?** Reading this privacy notice will help you understand your privacy rights and choices. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, please do not use our Services. If you still have any questions or concerns, please contact us at info@fishhook.us.

**SUMMARY OF KEY POINTS**

**_This summary provides key points from our privacy notice, but you can find out more details about any of these topics by clicking the link following each key point or by using our_** [**_table of contents_**](#toc) **_below to find the section you are looking for._**

**What personal information do we process?** When you visit, use, or navigate our Services, we may process personal information depending on how you interact with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. Learn more about [personal information you disclose to us](#personalinfo).

**Do we process any sensitive personal information?** We do not process sensitive personal information.

**Do we receive any information from third parties?** We may receive information from public databases, marketing partners, social media platforms, and other outside sources. Learn more about [information collected from other sources](#othersources).

**How do we process your information?** We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent. We process your information only when we have a valid legal reason to do so. Learn more about [how we process your information](#infouse).

**In what situations and with which types of parties do we share personal information?** We may share information in specific situations and with specific categories of third parties. Learn more about [when and with whom we share your personal information](#whoshare).

**How do we keep your information safe?** We have organizational and technical processes and procedures in place to protect your personal information. However, no electronic transmission over the internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Learn more about [how we keep your information safe](#infosafe).

**What are your rights?** Depending on where you are located geographically, the applicable privacy law may mean you have certain rights regarding your personal information. Learn more about [your privacy rights](#privacyrights).

**How do you exercise your rights?** The easiest way to exercise your rights is by visiting info@fishhook.us, or by contacting us. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

Want to learn more about what we do with any information we collect? [Review the privacy notice in full](#toc).

**TABLE OF CONTENTS**

[3\. WHAT LEGAL BASES DO WE RELY ON TO PROCESS YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?](#legalbases)

[4\. WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?](#whoshare)

[11\. DO UNITED STATES RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?](#uslaws)

[14\. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?](#request)

**1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

**Personal information you disclose to us**

**_In Short:_** _We collect personal information that you provide to us._

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and Services, when you participate in activities on the Services, or otherwise when you contact us.

**Personal Information Provided by You.** The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Services, the choices you make, and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect may include the following:

* names
* phone numbers
* email addresses
* job titles
* contact preferences
* mailing addresses

**Sensitive Information.** We do not process sensitive information.

All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete, and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.

**Information automatically collected**

**_In Short:_** _Some information — such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and/or browser and device characteristics — is collected automatically when you visit our Services._

We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use, or navigate the Services. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Services, and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Services, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.

The information we collect includes:

* _Log and Usage Data._ Log and usage data is service-related, diagnostic, usage, and performance information our servers automatically collect when you access or use our Services and which we record in log files. Depending on how you interact with us, this log data may include your IP address, device information, browser type, and settings and information about your activity in the Services (such as the date/time stamps associated with your usage, pages and files viewed, searches, and other actions you take such as which features you use), device event information (such as system activity, error reports (sometimes called "crash dumps"), and hardware settings).

* _Device Data._ We collect device data such as information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other device you use to access the Services. Depending on the device used, this device data may include information such as your IP address (or proxy server), device and application identification numbers, location, browser type, hardware model, Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, operating system, and system configuration information.

* _Location Data._ We collect location data such as information about your device's location, which can be either precise or imprecise. How much information we collect depends on the type and settings of the device you use to access the Services. For example, we may use GPS and other technologies to collect geolocation data that tells us your current location (based on your IP address). You can opt out of allowing us to collect this information either by refusing access to the information or by disabling your Location setting on your device. However, if you choose to opt out, you may not be able to use certain aspects of the Services.

**Information collected from other sources**

**_In Short:_** _We may collect limited data from public databases, marketing partners, and other outside sources._

In order to enhance our ability to provide relevant marketing, offers, and services to you and update our records, we may obtain information about you from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, affiliate programs, data providers, and from other third parties. This information includes mailing addresses, job titles, email addresses, phone numbers, intent data (or user behavior data), Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, social media profiles, social media URLs, and custom profiles, for purposes of targeted advertising and event promotion.

### Information Obtained Through Interactive Features and Third Party Integrations

We may engage vendors to provide certain interactive features on our Sites. Your use of these interactive features is voluntary, and we may retain the information that you submit through the features. For example, we may offer an interactive chat feature on our Sites to answer questions and for other customer service purposes. When you participate in the interactive chat, either with a virtual or live agent, the contents of the chat may be captured and kept as a transcript. By using these features, you understand that our vendors may process the information obtained through the feature to provide the service on our behalf.

You may disclose your own Personal Information on message boards, chats, profile pages, and other social networking features and services to which you are able to post information and materials. Please note that any information you post or disclose through these services may be available to visitors to the Sites and the general public, depending on the particular service and any privacy settings in place (such as through your profile).

We may offer third party integrations on our Sites. If you choose to connect a third party account to our system, you should refer to that party’s privacy policy for information on how your Personal Information is collected, used and protected. One such integration is YouTube API Services, which may collect, store, use, process and share Personal Information as described in this Policy. The YouTube API Services also may serve content and store, access and collect Personal Information from your devices as described in this Policy**.** Clients using our platforms are bound and agree to the [YouTube Terms of Service](https://www.youtube.com/static?template=terms). For more information about the YouTube API Services, please refer to the [**Google Privacy Policy**](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy). In addition to exercising your choices as described in this Policy and our Cookie Notice, you can revoke access to your Personal Information collected and processed through the YouTube API Services using Google’s security settings at [**https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions**](https://security.google.com/settings/security/permissions).

Our apps use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google APIs will adhere to [**Google API Services User Data Policy**](https://protect-us.mimecast.com/s/vFsGCBBpj1s13gpnHNR1Pn?domain=developers.google.com), including the Limited Use requirements.

**2\. HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_** _We process your information to provide, improve, and administer our Services, communicate with you, for security and fraud prevention, and to comply with law. We may also process your information for other purposes with your consent._

**We process your personal information for a variety of reasons, depending on how you interact with our Services, including:**

* **To deliver and facilitate delivery of services to the user.** We may process your information to provide you with the requested service.

* **To respond to user inquiries/offer support to users.** We may process your information to respond to your inquiries and solve any potential issues you might have with the requested service.

* **To send administrative information to you.** We may process your information to send you details about our products and services, changes to our terms and policies, and other similar information.

* **To send you marketing and promotional communications.** We may process the personal information you send to us for our marketing purposes, if this is in accordance with your marketing preferences. You can opt out of our marketing emails at any time. For more information, see "[WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?](#privacyrights)" below.

* **To deliver targeted advertising to you.** We may process your information to develop and display personalized content and advertising tailored to your interests, location, and more.

* **To evaluate and improve our Services, products, marketing, and your experience.** We may process your information when we believe it is necessary to identify usage trends, determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns, and to evaluate and improve our Services, products, marketing, and your experience.

* **To identify usage trends.** We may process information about how you use our Services to better understand how they are being used so we can improve them.

* **To determine the effectiveness of our marketing and promotional campaigns.** We may process your information to better understand how to provide marketing and promotional campaigns that are most relevant to you.

**3\. WHAT LEGAL BASES DO WE RELY ON TO PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?**

_**In Short:** We only process your personal information when we believe it is necessary and we have a valid legal reason (i.e., legal basis) to do so under applicable law, like with your consent, to comply with laws, to provide you with services to enter into or fulfill our contractual obligations, to protect your rights, or to fulfill our legitimate business interests._

**_If you are located in Canada, this section applies to you._**

We may process your information if you have given us specific permission (i.e., express consent) to use your personal information for a specific purpose, or in situations where your permission can be inferred (i.e., implied consent). You can [withdraw your consent](#withdrawconsent) at any time.

In some exceptional cases, we may be legally permitted under applicable law to process your information without your consent, including, for example:

* If collection is clearly in the interests of an individual and consent cannot be obtained in a timely way
* For investigations and fraud detection and prevention
* For business transactions provided certain conditions are met 
* If it is contained in a witness statement and the collection is necessary to assess, process, or settle an insurance claim 
* For identifying injured, ill, or deceased persons and communicating with next of kin 
* If we have reasonable grounds to believe an individual has been, is, or may be victim of financial abuse
* If it is reasonable to expect collection and use with consent would compromise the availability or the accuracy of the information and the collection is reasonable for purposes related to investigating a breach of an agreement or a contravention of the laws of Canada or a province
* If disclosure is required to comply with a subpoena, warrant, court order, or rules of the court relating to the production of records 
* If it was produced by an individual in the course of their employment, business, or profession and the collection is consistent with the purposes for which the information was produced
* If the collection is solely for journalistic, artistic, or literary purposes 
* If the information is publicly available and is specified by the regulations

**4\. WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_** _We may share information in specific situations described in this section and/or with the following categories of third parties._ 

**Vendors, Consultants, and Other Third-Party Service Providers.** We may share your data with third-party vendors, service providers, contractors, or agents ("**third parties**") who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. We have contracts in place with our third parties, which are designed to help safeguard your personal information. This means that they cannot do anything with your personal information unless we have instructed them to do it. They will also not share your personal information with any organization apart from us. They also commit to protect the data they hold on our behalf and to retain it for the period we instruct. The categories of third parties we may share personal information with are as follows:

* Ad Networks
* Communication & Collaboration Tools
* Data Analytics Services
* Performance Monitoring Tools
* Product Engineering & Design Tools
* Retargeting Platforms
* Sales & Marketing Tools
* Social Networks
* Website Hosting Service Providers

**5\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?**

**_In Short:_** _We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information._

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our Cookie Notice.

**6\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_** _We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy notice unless otherwise required by law._

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting, or other legal requirements).

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize such information, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**7\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?**

**_In Short:_** _We aim to protect your personal information through a system of organizational and technical security measures._

We have implemented appropriate and reasonable technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, despite our safeguards and efforts to secure your information, no electronic transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Services is at your own risk. You should only access the Services within a secure environment.

**8\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?**

**_In Short:_** _We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 18 years of age._

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Services, you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the Services. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we may have collected from children under age 18, please contact us at info@fishhook.us.

**9\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

**_In Short:_** _In some regions, such as Canada, you have rights that allow you greater access to and control over your personal information. You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time._

In some regions (like Canada), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; (iv) if applicable, to data portability; and (v) not to be subject to automated decision-making. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. You can make such a request by contacting us by using the contact details provided in the section "[HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](#contact)" below.

We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

**Withdrawing your consent:** If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, which may be express and/or implied consent depending on the applicable law, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You can withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us by using the contact details provided in the section "[HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](#contact)" below.

However, please note that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal nor, when applicable law allows, will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

**Opting out of marketing and promotional communications:** You can unsubscribe from our marketing and promotional communications at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the emails that we send, or by contacting us using the details provided in the section "[HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](#contact)" below. You will then be removed from the marketing lists. However, we may still communicate with you — for example, to send you service-related messages that are necessary for the administration and use of your account, to respond to service requests, or for other non-marketing purposes. 

**Cookies and similar technologies:** Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Services.

If you have questions or comments about your privacy rights, you may email us at info@fishhook.us.

**10\. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES**

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track ("DNT") feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. At this stage no uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy notice.

**11\. DO UNITED STATES RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

**_In Short:_** _If you are a resident of California, Colorado, Connecticut, Utah or Virginia, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal information._

**What categories of personal information do we collect?**

We have collected the following categories of personal information in the past twelve (12) months:

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Category** | **Examples** | **Collected** |
| A. Identifiers | Contact details, such as real name, alias, postal address, telephone or mobile contact number, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, and account name | YES |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| B. Personal information as defined in the California Customer Records statute | Name, contact information, education, employment, employment history, and financial information | YES |

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| C. Protected classification characteristics under state or federal law | Gender and date of birth | YES |
| D. Commercial information | Transaction information, purchase history, financial details, and payment information | NO  |
| E. Biometric information | Fingerprints and voiceprints | NO  |
| F. Internet or other similar network activity | Browsing history, search history, online behavior, interest data, and interactions with our and other websites, applications, systems, and advertisements | YES |
| G. Geolocation data | Device location | YES |
| H. Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information | Images and audio, video or call recordings created in connection with our business activities | NO  |
| I. Professional or employment-related information | Business contact details in order to provide you our Services at a business level or job title, work history, and professional qualifications if you apply for a job with us | YES |
| J. Education Information | Student records and directory information | NO  |
| K. Inferences drawn from collected personal information | Inferences drawn from any of the collected personal information listed above to create a profile or summary about, for example, an individual’s preferences and characteristics | YES |
| L. Sensitive personal Information |     | NO  |

We will use and retain the collected personal information as needed to provide the Services or for:

* Category A - As long as the user has an account with us
* Category B - As long as the user has an account with us
* Category C - As long as the user has an account with us
* Category F - As long as the user has an account with us
* Category G - As long as the user has an account with us
* Category I - As long as the user has an account with us
* Category K - As long as the user has an account with us

We may also collect other personal information outside of these categories through instances where you interact with us in person, online, or by phone or mail in the context of:

* Receiving help through our customer support channels;
* Participation in customer surveys or contests; and
* Facilitation in the delivery of our Services and to respond to your inquiries.

**How do we use and share your personal information?**

Learn about how we use your personal information in the section, "[HOW DO WE PROCESS YOUR INFORMATION?](#infouse)"

We collect and share your personal information through:

* Targeting cookies/Marketing cookies
* Social media cookies
* Beacons/Pixels/Tags

**Will your information be shared with anyone else?**

We may disclose your personal information with our service providers pursuant to a written contract between us and each service provider. Learn more about how we disclose personal information to in the section, "[WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?](#whoshare)"

We may use your personal information for our own business purposes, such as for undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration. This is not considered to be "selling" of your personal information.

We have not sold or shared any personal information to third parties for a business or commercial purpose in the preceding twelve (12) months. We have disclosed the following categories of personal information to third parties for a business or commercial purpose in the preceding twelve (12) months:  

The categories of third parties to whom we disclosed personal information for a business or commercial purpose can be found under "[WHEN AND WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?](#whoshare)"

**California Residents**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Services, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Services. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Services, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from all our systems (e.g., backups, etc.).

**CCPA Privacy Notice**

This section applies only to California residents. Under the California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), you have the rights listed below.

The California Code of Regulations defines a "residents" as:

(1) every individual who is in the State of California for other than a temporary or transitory purpose and

(2) every individual who is domiciled in the State of California who is outside the State of California for a temporary or transitory purpose

All other individuals are defined as "non-residents."

If this definition of "resident" applies to you, we must adhere to certain rights and obligations regarding your personal information.

**Your rights with respect to your personal data**

Right to request deletion of the data — Request to delete

You can ask for the deletion of your personal information. If you ask us to delete your personal information, we will respect your request and delete your personal information, subject to certain exceptions provided by law, such as (but not limited to) the exercise by another consumer of his or her right to free speech, our compliance requirements resulting from a legal obligation, or any processing that may be required to protect against illegal activities.

Right to be informed — Request to know

Depending on the circumstances, you have a right to know:

* whether we collect and use your personal information;
* the categories of personal information that we collect;
* the purposes for which the collected personal information is used;
* whether we sell or share personal information to third parties;
* the categories of personal information that we sold, shared, or disclosed for a business purpose;
* the categories of third parties to whom the personal information was sold, shared, or disclosed for a business purpose;
* the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing personal information; and
* the specific pieces of personal information we collected about you.

In accordance with applicable law, we are not obligated to provide or delete consumer information that is de-identified in response to a consumer request or to re-identify individual data to verify a consumer request.

Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of a Consumer’s Privacy Rights

We will not discriminate against you if you exercise your privacy rights.

Right to Limit Use and Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information

We do not process consumer's sensitive personal information.

Verification process

Upon receiving your request, we will need to verify your identity to determine you are the same person about whom we have the information in our system. These verification efforts require us to ask you to provide information so that we can match it with information you have previously provided us. For instance, depending on the type of request you submit, we may ask you to provide certain information so that we can match the information you provide with the information we already have on file, or we may contact you through a communication method (e.g., phone or email) that you have previously provided to us. We may also use other verification methods as the circumstances dictate.

We will only use personal information provided in your request to verify your identity or authority to make the request. To the extent possible, we will avoid requesting additional information from you for the purposes of verification. However, if we cannot verify your identity from the information already maintained by us, we may request that you provide additional information for the purposes of verifying your identity and for security or fraud-prevention purposes. We will delete such additionally provided information as soon as we finish verifying you.

Other privacy rights

* You may object to the processing of your personal information.
* You may request correction of your personal data if it is incorrect or no longer relevant, or ask to restrict the processing of the information.
* You can designate an authorized agent to make a request under the CCPA on your behalf. We may deny a request from an authorized agent that does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf in accordance with the CCPA.
* You may request to opt out from future selling or sharing of your personal information to third parties. Upon receiving an opt-out request, we will act upon the request as soon as feasibly possible, but no later than fifteen (15) days from the date of the request submission.

 To exercise these rights, you can contact us by visiting info@fishhook.us, by email at info@fishhook.us, or by referring to the contact details at the bottom of this document. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you.

**Colorado Residents**

This section applies only to Colorado residents. Under the Colorado Privacy Act (CPA), you have the rights listed below. However, these rights are not absolute, and in certain cases, we may decline your request as permitted by law.

* Right to be informed whether or not we are processing your personal data
* Right to access your personal data
* Right to correct inaccuracies in your personal data
* Right to request deletion of your personal data
* Right to obtain a copy of the personal data you previously shared with us
* Right to opt out of the processing of your personal data if it is used for targeted advertising, the sale of personal data, or profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects ("profiling")

To submit a request to exercise these rights described above, please email info@fishhook.us or visit info@fishhook.us.

If we decline to take action regarding your request and you wish to appeal our decision, please email us at info@fishhook.us. Within forty-five (45) days of receipt of an appeal, we will inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including a written explanation of the reasons for the decisions.

**Connecticut Residents**

This section applies only to Connecticut residents. Under the Connecticut Data Privacy Act (CTDPA), you have the rights listed below. However, these rights are not absolute, and in certain cases, we may decline your request as permitted by law.

* Right to be informed whether or not we are processing your personal data
* Right to access your personal data
* Right to correct inaccuracies in your personal data
* Right to request deletion of your personal data
* Right to obtain a copy of the personal data you previously shared with us
* Right to opt out of the processing of your personal data if it is used for targeted advertising, the sale of personal data, or profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects ("profiling")

 To submit a request to exercise these rights described above, please email info@fishhook.us or visit info@fishhook.us.

If we decline to take action regarding your request and you wish to appeal our decision, please email us at info@fishhook.us. Within sixty (60) days of receipt of an appeal, we will inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including a written explanation of the reasons for the decisions.

**Utah Residents**

This section applies only to Utah residents. Under the Utah Consumer Privacy Act (UCPA), you have the rights listed below. However, these rights are not absolute, and in certain cases, we may decline your request as permitted by law.

* Right to be informed whether or not we are processing your personal data
* Right to access your personal data
* Right to request deletion of your personal data
* Right to obtain a copy of the personal data you previously shared with us
* Right to opt out of the processing of your personal data if it is used for targeted advertising or the sale of personal data

To submit a request to exercise these rights described above, please email info@fishhook.us or visit info@fishhook.us.

**Virginia Residents**

Under the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act (VCDPA):

 "Consumer" means a natural person who is a resident of the Commonwealth acting only in an individual or household context. It does not include a natural person acting in a commercial or employment context.

 "Personal data" means any information that is linked or reasonably linkable to an identified or identifiable natural person. "Personal data" does not include de-identified data or publicly available information.

 "Sale of personal data" means the exchange of personal data for monetary consideration.

If this definition of "consumer" applies to you, we must adhere to certain rights and obligations regarding your personal data.

Your rights with respect to your personal data

* Right to be informed whether or not we are processing your personal data
* Right to access your personal data
* Right to correct inaccuracies in your personal data
* Right to request deletion of your personal data
* Right to obtain a copy of the personal data you previously shared with us
* Right to opt out of the processing of your personal data if it is used for targeted advertising, the sale of personal data, or profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal or similarly significant effects ("profiling") 

Exercise your rights provided under the Virginia VCDPA

 You may contact us by email at info@fishhook.us or visit info@fishhook.us.

If you are using an authorized agent to exercise your rights, we may deny a request if the authorized agent does not submit proof that they have been validly authorized to act on your behalf.

Verification process

We may request that you provide additional information reasonably necessary to verify you and your consumer's request. If you submit the request through an authorized agent, we may need to collect additional information to verify your identity before processing your request.

Upon receiving your request, we will respond without undue delay, but in all cases, within forty-five (45) days of receipt. The response period may be extended once by forty-five (45) additional days when reasonably necessary. We will inform you of any such extension within the initial 45-day response period, together with the reason for the extension.

Right to appeal

If we decline to take action regarding your request, we will inform you of our decision and reasoning behind it. If you wish to appeal our decision, please email us at info@fishhook.us. Within sixty (60) days of receipt of an appeal, we will inform you in writing of any action taken or not taken in response to the appeal, including a written explanation of the reasons for the decisions. If your appeal is denied, you may contact the [Attorney General to submit a complaint](https://www.oag.state.va.us/consumer-protection/index.php/file-a-complaint).

**12\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?**

_**In Short:** Yes, we will update this notice as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws._

We may update this privacy notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated "Revised" date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

**13\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?**

If you have questions or comments about this notice, you may email us at info@fishhook.us or contact us by post at:

Fishhook, Inc

9511 Angola Court, Ste 217

Indianapolis, IN 46268

United States

**14\. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?**

 Based on the applicable laws of your country, you may have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it. To request to review, update, or delete your personal information, please visit: info@fishhook.us.

This privacy policy was created using Termly's [Privacy Policy Generator](https://termly.io/products/privacy-policy-generator/).

_Policy updated on 10/25/2023_

### Stay Connected

Nexus Impact Center  
[9511 Angola Court, Ste 217  
Indianapolis, IN 46268](https://g.page/fishhookinc?share)

© Fishhook, Inc. All rights reserved. [Privacy Policy](https://www.fishhook.us/privacy-policy) | [Terms of Service](https://www.fishhook.us/tos)
